LESLIE PATINO

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

Self-motivated front-end developer with experience in digital design, full stack development, and management. This career path has required creativity, problem-solving, personal and team development, and professionalism. Additionally, I am bilingual in English and Spanish and aim to leverage my knowledge, skills, and strong work ethic to develop thoughtful and intelligent web applications.

EDUCATION

University of California Berkeley Extension Full Stack Web Development, 2021-2022

EXPERIENCE

Lifestyle Director

FirstService Residential, 2020-2021

- Budgeted, planned, facilitated and marketed for community events
- Hired, trained, and supervised concierge
- Head of all digital communication

Promotional Event Specialist 2013 - 2020

- Managed teams from 3-20 people
- Worked with Google, ESPN, HP, and BMW
- Chosen out of hundreds to lead regional tours for Volkswagen and Kroger.

Assistant Spa Director LifeTime Athletic, 2018 - 2019

- Implemented marketing strategies to increase revenue
- Reached locations' highest month of revenue during my time there
- Hired, trained, and supervised front desk

CONTACT

- Las Vegas, NV
- 702-763-1712
- lesliejpatino@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/lesliejpatino/
- github.com/lesliejpatino

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- React.js
- HTML
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- Javascript
- jQuery

- Server side API's
- Node
- Express
- mySql
- Sequelize
- Handlebars

PROJECTS

Ignite

- **Summary:** This application helps couples stay connected by igniting meaningful conversation and providing each partner personalized ideas to make the other feel loved, based on a questionnaire that we created.
- Role: Create questionnaire logic via Javascript, React, UI
- **Tech Stack:** MongoDB, Express, React, Node, Bootstrap
- **Live Site:** https://fierce-sands-31159.herokuapp.com/

Organizarr

- **Summary:** Created with the busy student in mind. Users access a personal dashboard where they can save notes, to-do lists and create/attend study groups.
- **Role:** Project management, design, UI, model creation, client-side Javascript, Handlebars, debugging.
- **Tech Stack:** Handlebars/HTML, Bootstrap/CSS, Javascript, Express, Node, Sequelize
- **Live Site:** dry-badlands-77030.herokuapp.com/

Map-A-Test: Find a Covid Testing Site Near You

- **Summary:** Through a simple and straightforward UI, this application displays covid testing sites based on location.
- Role: Third party API's, form validation, UI, Javascript.
- **Tech Stack:** HTML, Javascript, jQuery, Foundation/CSS, Parsley, Google and Covid API's
- Live Site: lesliejpatino.github.io/find-covid-testing/